<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Feature Guides on</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/feature-guides/</link><description>Recent content in Feature Guides on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/feature-guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Automata Plugins</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/feature-guides/automata-plugins/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/feature-guides/automata-plugins/</guid><description>The documentation on this page may be out of date. The contents of this document may reference older, obsolete NAM content. It, however, can still be used as a reference guide. Note:* The Automata Plugins are also referred as Automata Controllers, like other NAM files where only one file can be installed at a time.
IT IS IMPORTANT THAT YOU ONLY USE ONE OF THE &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;Automata_Plugin&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; FILES, &amp;amp; ONE ONLY.</description></item><item><title>Base Network Additions</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/feature-guides/base-network-additions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/feature-guides/base-network-additions/</guid><description>The documentation on this page may be out of date. The contents of this document may reference older, obsolete NAM content. It, however, can still be used as a reference guide. Some additional features, such as the RealHighways (RHW), Network Widening Mod (NWM), RealRailways (RRW), High Speed Rail Project (HSRP), Turn Lanes, and PedMalls are covered in the Feature Guides section of this documentation.
Additional Overpasses # Fully functional Overpasses.</description></item><item><title>Bridges</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/feature-guides/bridges/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/feature-guides/bridges/</guid><description>This documentation has not yet been written.</description></item><item><title>Canals</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/feature-guides/canals/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/feature-guides/canals/</guid><description>The documentation on this page is in progress. The contents of this document are undergoing revision and are subject to change. While CAN-AM is technically functional without any additional files, it is designed to work with either of the following (which are necessary for the canals to have walls):
CAL SG Canals by callagrafx (recommended) OR The original SG Canals by SimGoober The NAM CAN-AM files do include a single passenger station for use with CAN-AM.</description></item><item><title>Cosmetic Additions</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/feature-guides/cosmetic-additions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/feature-guides/cosmetic-additions/</guid><description>This documentation has not yet been written.</description></item><item><title>Data View Plugins</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/feature-guides/data-view-plugins/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/feature-guides/data-view-plugins/</guid><description>Information # This Traffic Volume View offers a number of improvements to the one included with the game. Rather than the seven shades of blue in the original, this version uses the full spectrum of color, including approximately 48 distinct color shades. The maximum volume shown for each travel type has been increased from a flat 1200 for all types in the original Traffic Volume View to a value which is 300% of the capacity of the underlying network for the selected travel type.</description></item><item><title>Flexible Underpasses</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/feature-guides/flexible-underpasses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/feature-guides/flexible-underpasses/</guid><description>New Method: Subway-based Draggable Override Network # The newest method for building Flexible Underpasses (FLUPs) involves the use of overrideable FLEX-based Portals, coupled with Subway-based draggable override networks, and overrideable FLEX-based overcrossing pieces. The new method currently supports tunnel portals for four networks in the RealHighway (RHW) plugin: the RHW-2, RHW-3, RHW-4, and the MIS Ramp.
The menu button used to access the Subway-based FLUPs content is located under the Highways menu, and it contains the items listed below:</description></item><item><title>High Speed Rail</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/feature-guides/high-speed-rail/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/feature-guides/high-speed-rail/</guid><description>Legacy Content This component of the Network Addon Mod has not been updated in some time. Active development is likely to resume in the future. In the early years of SC4, new technology was found by smoncrie which allowed us to use a single puzzle piece to create a starter for a new set of textures or models for the same network, there are already a few mods that take advantage of this technology, namely draggable GLR, SAM, and RHW.</description></item><item><title>Hybrid Railway</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/feature-guides/hybrid-railway/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/feature-guides/hybrid-railway/</guid><description>The Hybrid Railway, or HRW is an intermediate FLEX based network that provides for both heavy and High Speed (Monorail) traffic. Specifications of the HRW include catenaries, textures that are the same as the RRW, as well as including some purpose-built textures for specific pieces.
In terms of functionality, the HRW handles both Heavy Rail (in orange) and Monorail as shown (in dark blue) below.
The HRW is a FLEX network utilising dual-networking (Rail and Monorail) pieces meaning it can only be constructed with FLEX pieces provided in the menus.</description></item><item><title>Light Rail/Tram</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/feature-guides/light-rail-tram/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/feature-guides/light-rail-tram/</guid><description>Legacy Content This component of the Network Addon Mod has not been updated in some time. Active development is likely to resume in the future. The NAM&amp;rsquo;s feature additions to this area of the transportation system include numerous Dual-Networking options, allowing for Light Rail and Tram service to be placed in the median of, or over top of, various surface street networks, including Roads, Avenues, and Streets.
Installing the Light Rail/Tram Features from the NAM Installer # The various Light Rail/Tram features in the NAM are found in the NAM Installer under &amp;ldquo;2 Additional Network Features &amp;gt; Light Rail&amp;rdquo;.</description></item></channel></rss>