<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Riferimento on</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Riferimento on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Read First</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/reference/read-first/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/reference/read-first/</guid><description>Avviso di compatibilità - Copie EA App e Origin di SimCity 4 Deluxe Le copie digitali di SimCity 4 Deluxe acquistate tramite EA.com, l'App EA o l'Origin Store presentano un eseguibile non patchato che è inferiore ai requisiti minimi per questa mod. Lo stesso vale se si gioca con un abbonamento EA Play o Xbox Game Pass. Per saperne di più Contenuto non tradotto Questa documentazione non è ancora stata tradotta nella vostra lingua.</description></item><item><title>Note sull'installazione</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/reference/installation-notes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/reference/installation-notes/</guid><description>Avviso di compatibilità - Copie EA App e Origin di SimCity 4 Deluxe Le copie digitali di SimCity 4 Deluxe acquistate tramite EA.com, l'App EA o l'Origin Store presentano un eseguibile non patchato che è inferiore ai requisiti minimi per questa mod. Lo stesso vale se si gioca con un abbonamento EA Play o Xbox Game Pass. Per saperne di più Note sull&amp;rsquo;installazione # Innanzitutto, assicurarsi di aver estratto il contenuto di questo file .</description></item><item><title>In-Game Basics with the NAM</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/reference/in-game-basics/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/reference/in-game-basics/</guid><description>Contenuto non tradotto Questa documentazione non è ancora stata tradotta nella vostra lingua. Basic Types of Content # With respect to all the transportation network expansions within the NAM, they fall into two categories: Draggable Items, produced through dragging a transportation network in some fashion, and Ploppable Items, which are placed in a single click. Within these two categories, there are distinctions.
Subtypes of Draggable Items # Simple Draggable Items, which are constructed simply by dragging the network (or combination of networks) in an immediately apparent and intuitive manner.</description></item><item><title>Overview of Content and Features</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/reference/overview-of-content-and-features/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/reference/overview-of-content-and-features/</guid><description> La documentazione di questa pagina non è ancora stata scritta.</description></item><item><title>Frequently Asked Questions</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/reference/frequently-asked-questions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/reference/frequently-asked-questions/</guid><description>Contenuto non tradotto Questa documentazione non è ancora stata tradotta nella vostra lingua. What is the Network Addon Mod?
The Network Addon Mod, or NAM, is a transportation mod for SimCity 4 Deluxe/Rush Hour. It includes options for improved pathfinding accuracy and performance with the game&amp;rsquo;s traffic simulator, as well as a myriad of new transportation network options, and bugfixes for default content. It is basically an exhaustive community-made expansion pack.</description></item><item><title>Glossary</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/reference/glossary/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/reference/glossary/</guid><description>Contenuto non tradotto Questa documentazione non è ancora stata tradotta nella vostra lingua. NAM: Network Addon Mod. The Network Addon Mod is an extensive mod for SimCity 4 Deluxe/Rush Hour, which encompasses virtually all community-developed transport network content (excluding most third-party stations, cosmetic mods and Lot-based items).
ABEP: Arthur Berkhardt Expressway Project. An &amp;ldquo;April Fools Day&amp;rdquo; cosmetic mod produced by Tarkus for the RealHighway&amp;rsquo;s RHW-8S network, inspired by the episode of the American comedy series &amp;ldquo;Seinfeld&amp;rdquo; (Season 8, Episode 16, &amp;ldquo;The Pothole&amp;rdquo;).</description></item><item><title>NAM Version History</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/reference/nam-version-history/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 08:50:23 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/reference/nam-version-history/</guid><description>Contenuto non tradotto Questa documentazione non è ancora stata tradotta nella vostra lingua. Agile Releases (2020 and later) # Version 47 (27 March 2023) # Pedestrian Revolution Mod Features: The NAM Team is pleased to present the Classic Draggable Pedmalls, courtesy of Ulisse Wolf and Lucario Boricua. These come in 8 styles, 6 of which are equivalents to the Pedmall Puzzle Pieces, and introducing 2 new designs: the Retrowave Red Brick, inspired in the old brick texture used for the U-Rail in earlier NAM versions, and the Industrial Style, using the concrete surface typical of industrial lots.</description></item><item><title>Informazioni tecniche</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/reference/technical-information/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/reference/technical-information/</guid><description>La documentazione di questa pagina non è aggiornata. Questa documentazione è stata aggiornata l'ultima volta con una vecchia versione del NAM. È in fase di riscrittura. Sebbene sia destinato principalmente alle persone in grado di aprire i file associati alla NAM, contiene importanti informazioni sul gioco. Pertanto, le informazioni che seguono riguardano l&amp;rsquo;aspetto più tecnico e devono essere considerate solo come una fonte aggiuntiva di informazioni sui file del mod e/o sul gioco.</description></item><item><title>Crediti</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/reference/credits/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/reference/credits/</guid><description>Il team NAM e gli associati (membri attivi a partire dal NAM 44)
Bipin bladeberkman blaireric b22rian CaptCity compdude787 Durfsurn eggman121 EstGuy/Cheese Flann Girafe Haljackey IDS2 Indiana Joe Jiwoahn KaenOkami Kitsune Lucario Boricua matias93 McDuell metarvo mgb204 Naomi57 noahclem pierreh Ramona Brie rivit Ryan B. Tarkus TheCouncill0r/dicko6 Tyberius06 ulisse z Fondatori NAM
Redlotus the7trumpets Tropod Responsabile del team NAM
Tarkus Evangelista tecnologico di NAM
Haljackey NAM Logo
MadSim (original design) Ramona Brie (updated design) Programmatori di strumenti</description></item></channel></rss>