<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What is the Network Addon Mod?</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/what-is-the-nam/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/what-is-the-nam/</guid><description>FEATURES # NAM Traffic Simulator - From more realistic subway costs to smarter Sims, NAM features it&amp;rsquo;s own traffic simulator that improves efficiency, usage, pathfinding and realism across all networks. This feature is a huge improvement to the vanilla game. Automata Controller - A fancy name for vehicles. It was important to update how the game processes vehicles with all the changes NAM provides. This feature with NAM allows you choose how many vehicles you want on your roads.</description></item><item><title>Installation</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/installation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/installation/</guid><description>Compatibility Notice - EA App and Origin Copies of SimCity 4 Deluxe NOW COMPATIBLE with the Network Addon Mod Digital copies of SimCity 4 Deluxe purchased via EA.com, the EA App, or the Origin Store have been patched to Version 1.1.641 as of 1 June 2023, and are now fully compatible with the Network Addon Mod. The same is true if playing the game via an EA Play or Xbox Game Pass subscription.</description></item><item><title>The Basics</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/in-game-basics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/in-game-basics/</guid><description>DRAGGABLE, PLOPPABLE! # Just like many other elements of Sim City 4, the many options in the NAM are either &amp;ldquo;draggable&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;ploppable&amp;rdquo;. Draggable items work just like the default networks: click, and drag to build them. Ploppable items work just like buildings in the menu: click to place them.
Simply put: drag a highway, plop a junction! Seem familiar?
OVERRIDES # The one particular difference with the NAM from other mods are items called Overrides.</description></item><item><title>Frequently Asked Questions</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/frequently-asked-questions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/frequently-asked-questions/</guid><description>What is the Network Addon Mod? # Take a peek at the Overview page.
What is the difference between NAM and NAMLite? # NAMLite is a bite-sized package for users looking for a minimal install. Think of NAMLite as a collection of the NAM&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;best hits&amp;rdquo;.
What all is included in the NAM? # Check out the Content Overview page for a brief look, and the full Features section of this documentation for a more in-depth look.</description></item><item><title>Troubleshooting (NAM Installation)</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/troubleshooting-installation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 21:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/troubleshooting-installation/</guid><description>What should I do if the NAM does not support my copy of the game? # The new NAM installer (introduced with the NAM 37 Release Candidate) no longer runs a version check. However, it is strongly recommended that users check the version they are running, as unpatched copies can be unstable. Version 1.1.610 and Version 1.1.613 are NOT supported.
In Case F, the solution is simply to install the EP1 Update 1 patch, which can be downloaded from EA (SKU 1-5), SimCity 4 Devotion (SKU 1-5), or Simtropolis (SKU 1 and 2 only).</description></item><item><title>Troubleshooting (Gameplay)</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/troubleshooting-gameplay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/troubleshooting-gameplay/</guid><description>Why is my game crashing when I try to load a city? # If you&amp;rsquo;re on Windows (or Linux) and the game crashes on your first attempt to load a city, this means you have the Full 4GB Controller installed, but either have experienced a failure in the 4GB Patch installation process, or have an incompatible system (not enough RAM and/or a 32-bit operating system). Either attempt to reinstall the 4GB Patch, or choose a less intensive installation option (the Low RAM/No RHW option, or download NAM Lite instead).</description></item></channel></rss>