<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Start Here</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/start-here/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/start-here/</guid><description>What is the Network Addon Mod? # The Network Addon Mod, or NAM, is a transportation mod for SimCity 4 Deluxe/Rush Hour. Most notably, NAM introduces hundreds of new network options, ranging from highways, railways, bridges, pedestrian malls and a lot more. Additionally, the mod greatly improves the game’s traffic simulator, bringing a whole new level of accuracy and performance.
Where do I start? # Right here, of course!</description></item><item><title>Installation</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/installation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/installation/</guid><description>Compatibility Notice - EA App and Origin Copies of SimCity 4 Deluxe NOW COMPATIBLE with the Network Addon Mod Digital copies of SimCity 4 Deluxe purchased via EA.com, the EA App, or the Origin Store have been patched to Version 1.1.641 as of 1 June 2023, and are now fully compatible with the Network Addon Mod. The same is true if playing the game via an EA Play or Xbox Game Pass subscription.</description></item><item><title>The Basics</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/in-game-basics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/in-game-basics/</guid><description>DRAGGABLE, PLOPPABLE! # Just like many other elements of Sim City 4, the many options in the NAM are used by either “dragging” or “plopping”.
Simply put: drag a highway, plop a junction! Seem familiar?
OVERRIDES # There is one particular difference with the NAM from other mods and they are called Overrides. Many elements in the NAM are designed to be plopped and then dragged through. When this happens, they transform their initial appearance, updating and fitting itself into your design, overiding into a single, seamless network.</description></item><item><title>Overview of NAM</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/overview-of-content-and-features/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/overview-of-content-and-features/</guid><description>Before we get too deep into the weeds, let&amp;rsquo;s do a brief overview of everything that NAM includes.
Alongside the new elements NAM gives you, there&amp;rsquo;s some important things it changes to the game. Meaning some new:
FEATURES # NAM Traffic Simulator - From more realistic subway costs to smarter Sims, NAM features it&amp;rsquo;s own traffic simulator that improves efficiency, usage, pathfinding and realism across all networks. This feature is a huge improvement to the vanilla game.</description></item><item><title>Frequently Asked Questions</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/frequently-asked-questions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/getting-started/frequently-asked-questions/</guid><description>What is the Network Addon Mod? If you do not know the answer to this, that means you&amp;rsquo;ve skipped the very important Start Here page.
What is the difference between NAM and NAMLite? NAMLite is a bite-sized package for users looking for a minimal install. Think of NAMLite as a &amp;ldquo;best hits&amp;rdquo;.
Why is my game crashing to desktop when I load a city tile after installing this mod?</description></item></channel></rss>