<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Guide alle funzioni on</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/feature-guides/</link><description>Recent content in Guide alle funzioni on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/feature-guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Automata Plugins</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/feature-guides/automata-plugins/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/feature-guides/automata-plugins/</guid><description>La documentazione di questa pagina potrebbe non essere obsoleta. Il contenuto di questo documento può fare riferimento a contenuti NAM più vecchi e obsoleti. Tuttavia, può ancora essere utilizzato come guida di riferimento. Contenuto non tradotto. Questa documentazione non è ancora stata tradotta nella vostra lingua. Note:* The Automata Plugins are also referred as Automata Controllers, like other NAM files where only one file can be installed at a time.</description></item><item><title>Base Network Additions</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/feature-guides/base-network-additions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/feature-guides/base-network-additions/</guid><description>La documentazione di questa pagina potrebbe non essere obsoleta. Il contenuto di questo documento può fare riferimento a contenuti NAM più vecchi e obsoleti. Tuttavia, può ancora essere utilizzato come guida di riferimento. Contenuto non tradotto. Questa documentazione non è ancora stata tradotta nella vostra lingua. Some additional features, such as the RealHighways (RHW), Network Widening Mod (NWM), RealRailways (RRW), High Speed Rail Project (HSRP), Turn Lanes, and PedMalls are covered in the Feature Guides section of this documentation.</description></item><item><title>Bridges</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/feature-guides/bridges/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/feature-guides/bridges/</guid><description>This documentation has not yet been written.</description></item><item><title>Canals</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/feature-guides/canals/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/feature-guides/canals/</guid><description>La documentazione di questa pagina è in corso di elaborazione. I contenuti di questo documento sono in fase di revisione e sono soggetti a modifiche. Contenuto non tradotto. Questa documentazione non è ancora stata tradotta nella vostra lingua. While CAN-AM is technically functional without any additional files, it is designed to work with either of the following (which are necessary for the canals to have walls):
CAL SG Canals by callagrafx (recommended) OR The original SG Canals by SimGoober The NAM CAN-AM files do include a single passenger station for use with CAN-AM.</description></item><item><title>Cosmetic Additions</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/feature-guides/cosmetic-additions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/feature-guides/cosmetic-additions/</guid><description>This documentation has not yet been written.</description></item><item><title>Data View Plugins</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/feature-guides/data-view-plugins/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/feature-guides/data-view-plugins/</guid><description>Contenuto non tradotto. Questa documentazione non è ancora stata tradotta nella vostra lingua. Information # This Traffic Volume View offers a number of improvements to the one included with the game. Rather than the seven shades of blue in the original, this version uses the full spectrum of color, including approximately 48 distinct color shades. The maximum volume shown for each travel type has been increased from a flat 1200 for all types in the original Traffic Volume View to a value which is 300% of the capacity of the underlying network for the selected travel type.</description></item><item><title>Flexible Underpasses</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/feature-guides/flexible-underpasses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/feature-guides/flexible-underpasses/</guid><description>Contenuto non tradotto. Questa documentazione non è ancora stata tradotta nella vostra lingua. New Method: Subway-based Draggable Override Network # The newest method for building Flexible Underpasses (FLUPs) involves the use of overrideable FLEX-based Portals, coupled with Subway-based draggable override networks, and overrideable FLEX-based overcrossing pieces. The new method currently supports tunnel portals for four networks in the RealHighway (RHW) plugin: the RHW-2, RHW-3, RHW-4, and the MIS Ramp.</description></item><item><title>High Speed Rail</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/feature-guides/high-speed-rail/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/feature-guides/high-speed-rail/</guid><description>Questa documentazione copre contenuti legacy. Questo componente del Network Addon Mod non viene aggiornato da tempo. È probabile che lo sviluppo attivo riprenda in futuro. Contenuto non tradotto. Questa documentazione non è ancora stata tradotta nella vostra lingua. In the early years of SC4, new technology was found by smoncrie which allowed us to use a single puzzle piece to create a starter for a new set of textures or models for the same network, there are already a few mods that take advantage of this technology, namely draggable GLR, SAM, and RHW.</description></item><item><title>Hybrid Railway</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/feature-guides/hybrid-railway/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/feature-guides/hybrid-railway/</guid><description>Contenuto non tradotto. Questa documentazione non è ancora stata tradotta nella vostra lingua. The Hybrid Railway, or HRW is an intermediate FLEX based network that provides for both heavy and High Speed (Monorail) traffic. Specifications of the HRW include catenaries, textures that are the same as the RRW, as well as including some purpose-built textures for specific pieces.
In terms of functionality, the HRW handles both Heavy Rail (in orange) and Monorail as shown (in dark blue) below.</description></item><item><title>Light Rail/Tram</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/feature-guides/light-rail-tram/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/it/docs/feature-guides/light-rail-tram/</guid><description>Questa documentazione copre contenuti legacy. Questo componente del Network Addon Mod non viene aggiornato da tempo. È probabile che lo sviluppo attivo riprenda in futuro. Contenuto non tradotto. Questa documentazione non è ancora stata tradotta nella vostra lingua. The NAM&amp;rsquo;s feature additions to this area of the transportation system include numerous Dual-Networking options, allowing for Light Rail and Tram service to be placed in the median of, or over top of, various surface street networks, including Roads, Avenues, and Streets.</description></item></channel></rss>