<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Glossary</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/glossary/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/glossary/</guid><description>NAM: Network Addon Mod. The Network Addon Mod is an extensive mod for SimCity 4 Deluxe/Rush Hour, which encompasses virtually all community-developed transport network content (excluding most third-party stations, cosmetic mods and Lot-based items).
ABEP: Arthur Berkhardt Expressway Project. An &amp;ldquo;April Fools Day&amp;rdquo; cosmetic mod produced by Tarkus for the RealHighway&amp;rsquo;s RHW-8S network, inspired by the episode of the American comedy series &amp;ldquo;Seinfeld&amp;rdquo; (Season 8, Episode 16, &amp;ldquo;The Pothole&amp;rdquo;).</description></item><item><title>NAM Version History</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/nam-version-history/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 08:50:23 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/nam-version-history/</guid><description>Transitional Releases (2024 through 2025)'' # Version 49 (2 March 2025) # Bridge Additions and Improvements: Red Truss Arch, Yellow Steel Girder, Green Truss, and Blue Supsension Bridges by IDS2 have been added for Road, Street, One-Way Road, AVE-2, ARD-3, NRD-4, OWR-3, RHW-2, RHW-3, RHW-4, and SAM Sets 2 and 6-11 (68 bridges total). Viaduct Bridges by Kitsune added at L3-L4 for MIS, RHW-4, and RHW-6S, and L0-L2 for Dual RHW-4 and RHW-6S (12 bridges total).</description></item><item><title>NAM Lite Version History</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/nam-lite-version-history/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/nam-lite-version-history/</guid><description>Version 4 (2 March 2025) # The issue with the Custom Interchanges button not allowing one to access more than just a single interchange type has been addressed (thanks to /u/Fart_Bard on /r/simcity4 for the report). NAM Lite&amp;rsquo;s file architecture has been better harmonized with that of the full edition of the NAM. Fixes lingering issue (since NAM Lite 3) with the Avenue Roundabouts button and adds the Roundabout path fixes that were also incorporated into NAM 49.</description></item><item><title>Technical Information</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/technical-information/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/technical-information/</guid><description>The documentation on this page is out of date. This documentation was last updated with an old version of the NAM. It is in the process of being rewritten. While it is mainly intended for persons with the skills to open the NAM&amp;rsquo;s associated file(s), it contains important information about the game. Therefore the following information aims at the more technical side of things and should only be considered as an additional source of information about the mods&amp;rsquo; files &amp;amp;/or game.</description></item><item><title>Credits</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/credits/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/credits/</guid><description>The NAM Team and Associates (Active Members as of NAM 49)
Abigail b22rian CaptCity DebussyMan dragonsteincole Durfsurn eggman121 Eric Blair EstGuy/Cheese Flann Girafe Haljackey hugues aroux IDS2 Indiana Joe KaenOkami/Amaterasu Kel9509 Kitsune Lucario Boricua matias93 McDuell memo metarvo mgb204 MushyMushy nos. 17 null45 pierreh Ramona Brie ReLynx/RemRinka rivit Ryan B. saus tartar Shadow Assassin Simizen smf_16 Tarkus Tyberius06 Ulisse Wolf NAM Founders
Redlotus the7trumpets Tropod NAM Logo
MadSim (original design) Ramona Brie (updated design) NAM Documentation Website</description></item></channel></rss>