<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Read First</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/read-first/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/read-first/</guid><description>Compatibility Warning - EA App and Origin Copies of SimCity 4 Deluxe Digital copies of SimCity 4 Deluxe purchased via EA.com, the EA App, or the Origin Store feature an unpatched executable that is below the minimum requirements for this mod. The same is true if playing the game via an EA Play or Xbox Game Pass subscription. Read more Compatibility and Installation # Before attempting to run the NAM installer, ensure that you have extracted the contents of the .</description></item><item><title>Installation Notes</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/installation-notes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/installation-notes/</guid><description>Compatibility Warning - EA App and Origin Copies of SimCity 4 Deluxe Digital copies of SimCity 4 Deluxe purchased via EA.com, the EA App, or the Origin Store feature an unpatched executable that is below the minimum requirements for this mod. The same is true if playing the game via an EA Play or Xbox Game Pass subscription. Read more Installation Notes # The minimum requirements for running the Network Addon Mod are as follows:</description></item><item><title>In-Game Basics with the NAM</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/in-game-basics/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/in-game-basics/</guid><description>Basic Types of Content # With respect to all the transportation network expansions within the NAM, they fall into two categories: Draggable Items, produced through dragging a transportation network in some fashion, and Ploppable Items, which are placed in a single click. Within these two categories, there are distinctions.
Subtypes of Draggable Items # Simple Draggable Items, which are constructed simply by dragging the network (or combination of networks) in an immediately apparent and intuitive manner.</description></item><item><title>Overview of Content and Features</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/overview-of-content-and-features/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/overview-of-content-and-features/</guid><description> The documentation on this page has not yet been written.</description></item><item><title>Frequently Asked Questions</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/frequently-asked-questions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/frequently-asked-questions/</guid><description>What is the Network Addon Mod?
The Network Addon Mod, or NAM, is a transportation mod for SimCity 4 Deluxe/Rush Hour. It includes options for improved pathfinding accuracy and performance with the game&amp;rsquo;s traffic simulator, as well as a myriad of new transportation network options, and bugfixes for default content. It is basically an exhaustive community-made expansion pack.
What is required to run the NAM?
You must be running a retail copy of SimCity 4 Deluxe OR SimCity 4 with the Rush Hour Expansion, with a version number of 1.</description></item><item><title>Glossary</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/glossary/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/glossary/</guid><description>NAM: Network Addon Mod. The Network Addon Mod is an extensive mod for SimCity 4 Deluxe/Rush Hour, which encompasses virtually all community-developed transport network content (excluding most third-party stations, cosmetic mods and Lot-based items).
ABEP: Arthur Berkhardt Expressway Project. An &amp;ldquo;April Fools Day&amp;rdquo; cosmetic mod produced by Tarkus for the RealHighway&amp;rsquo;s RHW-8S network, inspired by the episode of the American comedy series &amp;ldquo;Seinfeld&amp;rdquo; (Season 8, Episode 16, &amp;ldquo;The Pothole&amp;rdquo;).</description></item><item><title>NAM Version History</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/nam-version-history/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 08:50:23 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/nam-version-history/</guid><description>Agile Releases (2020 and later) # Version 47 (27 March 2023) # Pedestrian Revolution Mod Features: The NAM Team is pleased to present the Classic Draggable Pedmalls, courtesy of Ulisse Wolf and Lucario Boricua. These come in 8 styles, 6 of which are equivalents to the Pedmall Puzzle Pieces, and introducing 2 new designs: the Retrowave Red Brick, inspired in the old brick texture used for the U-Rail in earlier NAM versions, and the Industrial Style, using the concrete surface typical of industrial lots.</description></item><item><title>Technical Information</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/technical-information/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/technical-information/</guid><description>The documentation on this page is out of date. This documentation was last updated with an old version of the NAM. It is in the process of being rewritten. While it is mainly intended for persons with the skills to open the NAM&amp;rsquo;s associated file(s), it contains important information about the game. Therefore the following information aims at the more technical side of things and should only be considered as an additional source of information about the mods&amp;rsquo; files &amp;amp;/or game.</description></item><item><title>Credits</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/credits/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/credits/</guid><description>The following named members of Simtropolis, SC4 Devotion, SimCityPlaza, and the SC4 Devotion Discord have, for whatever particular reason, been specifically included here for their special contributions during the NAM&amp;rsquo;s history. Very special thanks goes towards them in the making, supplying, &amp;amp;/or supporting of this mod &amp;amp;/or its contents possible in one way shape or another:
The NAM Team and Associates (Active Members as of NAM 47)
Bipin bladeberkman b22rian CaptCity compdude787 DebussyMan Durfsurn eggman121 Eric Blair EstGuy/Cheese Flann Girafe Haljackey IDS2 Indiana Joe Junspud KaenOkami Kitsune Lucario Boricua matias93 McDuell memo metarvo mgb204 MushyMushy Naomi57 noahclem pierreh Ramona Brie ReLynx/RemRinka rivit Ryan B.</description></item></channel></rss>