<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Read First</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/read-first/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/read-first/</guid><description>Compatibility Warning - EA App and Origin Copies of SimCity 4 Deluxe This mod is NOT compatible with the EA App/Origin editions of SimCity 4 Deluxe (as sold on EA.com, and also available via EA play and Xbox Game Pass).
Do NOT run other versions of SimCity 4 Deluxe (i.e. Steam or GOG) with the EA App or its background processes running, as it is capable of unpatching Steam and GOG copies via its repair operations, making them incompatible.</description></item><item><title>Installation Notes</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/installation-notes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/installation-notes/</guid><description>Before beginning installation, make sure you have the following installed:
Java Runtime Environment (available from AdoptOpenJDK&amp;ndash;a 64-bit Windows copy of JRE 11 is enclosed in the download) Note: in order to ensure proper installation of NAM releases using the current installer, please remove the &amp;ldquo;Network Addon Mod&amp;rdquo; folder (and if still present, &amp;ldquo;z___NAM&amp;rdquo; folder) from the Plugins directory (usually My Documents\SimCity 4\Plugins on Windows) before installing a new NAM version. The Cleanup/Cleanitol functionality is not presently designed to remove full NAM installations.</description></item><item><title>In-Game Basics with the NAM</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/in-game-basics-with-the-nam/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/in-game-basics-with-the-nam/</guid><description>Basic Types of Content # With respect to all the transportation network expansions within the NAM, they fall into two categories: Draggable Items, produced through dragging a transportation network in some fashion, and Ploppable Items, which are placed in a single click. Within these two categories, there are distinctions.
Subtypes of Draggable Items # Simple Draggable Items, which are constructed simply by dragging the network (or combination of networks) in an immediately apparent and intuitive manner.</description></item><item><title>Overview of Content and Features</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/overview-of-content-and-features/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/overview-of-content-and-features/</guid><description>This section is still undergoing revision as of the NAM 36 release of September 2017.</description></item><item><title>Frequently Asked Questions</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/frequently-asked-questions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/frequently-asked-questions/</guid><description>What is the Network Addon Mod?
The Network Addon Mod, or NAM, is a transportation mod for SimCity 4 Deluxe/Rush Hour. It includes options for improved pathfinding accuracy and performance with the game&amp;rsquo;s traffic simulator, as well as a myriad of new transportation network options, and bugfixes for default content. It is basically an exhaustive community-made expansion pack.
What is required to run the NAM?
You must be running a retail copy of SimCity 4 Deluxe/Rush Hour, with a version number of 1.</description></item><item><title>Glossary</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/glossary/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/glossary/</guid><description>CAN-AM - Acronym for CANal Addon Mod.
DIPs - Acronym for Distilled Intersection Path s.
FTL - Acronym for FLEX Turn Lanes.
GLR - Acronym for Ground Light Rail, also sometimes known as the &amp;ldquo;Tram&amp;rdquo; network.
HSRP - Acronym for High Speed Rail Project.
NAM - Acronym for Network Addon Mod.
NWM - Acronym for Network Widening Mod.
OWR - Acronym for One- Way Road, referring to both the default transportation network, and its Network Widening Mod expansions (i.</description></item><item><title>NAM Version History</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/nam-version-history/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 08:50:23 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/nam-version-history/</guid><description>Agile Releases (2020 and later) # Version 44 (22 March 2022) # Hybrid Railway (HRW) Features: The Hybrid Railway system now features FA-2 Alt content, new textures to blend with the RealRailway (RRW) system, improvements to catenaries, and major improvements to Left-Hand Drive [LHD] support. RealHighway (RHW) x Avenue Features: The RealHighway (RHW) now has a FlexDDI system, allowing for FLEX-based Diverging Diamond interchanges with the Avenue network at ground level, and L1 and L2 elevations.</description></item><item><title>Technical Information</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/technical-information/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/technical-information/</guid><description>Note that this document is still in the process of transitioning to the new format introduced in NAM 36, and may contain some outdated information. While it is mainly intended for persons with the skills to open the NAM&amp;rsquo;s associated file(s), it contains important information about the game. Therefore the following information aims at the more technical side of things and should only be considered as an additional source of information about the mods&amp;rsquo; files &amp;amp;/or game.</description></item><item><title>Credits</title><link>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/credits/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sc4nam.com/docs/reference/credits/</guid><description>The NAM Team and Associates (Active Members as of NAM 44)
Bipin bladeberkman blaireric b22rian CaptCity compdude787 Durfsurn eggman121 EstGuy/Cheese Flann Girafe Haljackey IDS2 Indiana Joe Jiwoahn KaenOkami Kitsune Lucario Boricua matias93 McDuell metarvo mgb204 Naomi57 noahclem pierreh Ramona Brie rivit Ryan B. Tarkus TheCouncill0r/dicko6 Tyberius06 ulisse z NAM Founders
Redlotus the7trumpets Tropod NAM Team Lead
Tarkus NAM Technology Evangelist
Haljackey NAM Logo
MadSim (original design) Ramona Brie (updated design) Tool Programmers</description></item></channel></rss>